{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225399246","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225399246"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_130948"," gameId":" 6f639946-c967-4312-8f42-49eb74d0a69a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-12-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225415767","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225415766"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_130948"," gameId":" 6f639946-c967-4312-8f42-49eb74d0a69a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-12-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225424603","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225424603"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_130948"," gameId":" 6f639946-c967-4312-8f42-49eb74d0a69a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-12-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225432428","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225432428"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_130948"," gameId":" 6f639946-c967-4312-8f42-49eb74d0a69a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-12-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225442886","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225442884"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_130948"," gameId":" 6f639946-c967-4312-8f42-49eb74d0a69a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-12-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225474655","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225474655"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_130948"," gameId":" fa6f0878-2c60-4424-a313-ea41a04ed460"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_0-1-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225480912","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225480912"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_130948"," gameId":" fa6f0878-2c60-4424-a313-ea41a04ed460"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_0-1-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225485207","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225485207"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_130948"," gameId":" fa6f0878-2c60-4424-a313-ea41a04ed460"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-11-4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225491453","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225491453"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_130948"," gameId":" fa6f0878-2c60-4424-a313-ea41a04ed460"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-11-4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225497481","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225497480"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_130948"," gameId":" fa6f0878-2c60-4424-a313-ea41a04ed460"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-11-4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225501933","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225501933"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_130948"," gameId":" fa6f0878-2c60-4424-a313-ea41a04ed460"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_9-10-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225507633","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225507633"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_130948"," gameId":" fa6f0878-2c60-4424-a313-ea41a04ed460"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_9-10-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225513201","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225513200"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_130948"," gameId":" fa6f0878-2c60-4424-a313-ea41a04ed460"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_9-10-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225517135","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225517135"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_130948"," gameId":" fa6f0878-2c60-4424-a313-ea41a04ed460"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-1-11"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225521124","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225521124"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_130948"," gameId":" fa6f0878-2c60-4424-a313-ea41a04ed460"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-10-5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225526724","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225526724"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_130948"," gameId":" fa6f0878-2c60-4424-a313-ea41a04ed460"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-10-5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225533420","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225533420"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_130948"," gameId":" fa6f0878-2c60-4424-a313-ea41a04ed460"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-10-5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225540469","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225540469"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_130948"," gameId":" fa6f0878-2c60-4424-a313-ea41a04ed460"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-3-5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225544507","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225544506"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_130948"," gameId":" fa6f0878-2c60-4424-a313-ea41a04ed460"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-11-7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225548264","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225548263"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_130948"," gameId":" fa6f0878-2c60-4424-a313-ea41a04ed460"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_9-3-12"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225563340","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225563340"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_130948"," gameId":" fa6f0878-2c60-4424-a313-ea41a04ed460"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_3_9-3-12"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225569433","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225569433"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_130948"," gameId":" fa6f0878-2c60-4424-a313-ea41a04ed460"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_3_9-3-12"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225587208","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225587207"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_130948"," gameId":" fa6f0878-2c60-4424-a313-ea41a04ed460"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_3_9-3-12"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225587276","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225587275"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_130948"," gameId":" b1a60594-1053-4b1c-9fae-5961e0d313ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_68"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kalabushe alikuwa chiriku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHIRIKU"," userResponse":" CHIRIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}